{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was contemporary with Mihai Eminescu?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Ion Creangă and I.L Caragiale",
          "Ion Iliescu",
          "Viorel Lis"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Ion Creangă and I.L Caragiale"
      },
      {
        "question": "How did Mihai Eminescu's girlfriend call her?",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Sânziana Micle",
          "Dana Criminala",
          "Veronica Micle"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Veronica Micle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the literary society Mihai Eminescu was part of?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Masonry",
          "Dacia Literara",
          "Junimea"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Junimea"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the magazine in which the most important poems of Mihai Eminescu appeared?",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Dilema Veche Magazine",
          "Taifasuri Magazine",
          "Magazine Conversations Magazine"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Magazine Conversations Magazine"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of Mihai Eminescu's birth at birth?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Eminescovici",
          "Eminovici",
          "Eminevici"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Eminovici"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many letters did Mihai Eminescu write?",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "4, the rest were lost at the Post",
          "5 letters",
          "3, the rest are postcards"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "5 letters"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many stories does Lukeafarul's poem written by Mihai Eminescu?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "94 Stripes",
          "98 Stripes",
          "100 Stripes"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "98 Stripes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What's the fantastic short story written by Mihai Eminescu?",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Bad Dionys",
          "Bossul Dionys",
          "Poor Dionys"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Poor Dionys"
      },
      {
        "question": "At what age did Mihai Eminescu die?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "39 years old",
          "40 years old",
          "41 years old"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "39 years old"
      },
      {
        "question": "When was he born?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "January 20, 1850",
          "January 15, 1850",
          "January 15, 1851"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "January 15, 1850"
      },
      {
        "question": "When did he die?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "June 15, 1889",
          "June 16, 1890",
          "July 15, 1889"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "June 15, 1889"
      },
      {
        "question": "In what year does he meet Ion Creanga?",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "In 1875",
          "In 1885",
          "In 1890"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "In 1875"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where was he born?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Alba Iulia",
          "Suceava",
          "Botosani"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Botosani"
      },
      {
        "question": "In what year is the school inspector in Iasi and Vaslui?",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "in 1875",
          "in 1883",
          "in 1878"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "in 1875"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Mihai Eminescu?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "a poet",
          "a painter",
          "a musician"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a poet"
      },
      {
        "question": "Eminescu is the ... child of the family.",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "5th",
          "8th",
          "7th"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "7th"
      },
      {
        "question": "What's the name of Mihai Eminescu's father?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Ioan Eminescu",
          "Valeriu Eminoviciu",
          "Gheorghe Eminovici"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Gheorghe Eminovici"
      },
      {
        "question": "How does Mihai Eminescu call her mother?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Veronica",
          "Raluca",
          "Maria"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Raluca"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many brothers did Mihai Eminescu have?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "9 Brothers",
          "8 brothers",
          "10 brothers"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "10 brothers"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who did he fight to stop publishing the post of Mihai Eminescu?",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "with Iacob Negruzzi",
          "with Titu Maiorescu",
          "with Aron Pumnul"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "with Titu Maiorescu"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many sisters did Mihai Eminescu have?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "4 Sisters",
          "3 Sisters",
          "2 Sisters"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "4 Sisters"
      },
      {
        "question": "What's the name of the disease that the two sisters of Mihai Eminescu suffer?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "typhus",
          "Measles",
          "the plague"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "typhus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the two sisters will hate Mihai Eminescu at the moment when the disease is established?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Aglae, the older sister",
          "Henrieta, the younger sister",
          "Both"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Henrieta, the younger sister"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where did Mihai Eminescu's childhood spend?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "at Ipotesti",
          "at Medeleni",
          "at Flamanzi"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "at Ipotesti"
      },
      {
        "question": "How was Professor Mihai Eminescu's name?",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Ion G. Sbiera",
          "Iacob Negruzzi",
          "Aron Pumnul"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Aron Pumnul"
      },
      {
        "question": "To what society does Mihai Eminescu adhere?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Junimea",
          "East",
          "Time"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Junimea"
      },
      {
        "question": "Returning to the country in Iasi, Mihai Eminescu is named in 1874 director of ...",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Central Library",
          "Junimea Society",
          "School Inspectorate"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Central Library"
      },
      {
        "question": "When Mihai Eminescu met Ion Creanga, with whom he was to establish a lasting friendship, Mihai Eminescu was ...",
        "difficult": "Hard",
        "allAnswers": [
          "director of Iasi School Inspectorate",
          "School Reviewer (1875-1876)",
          "Director of the Central Library"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "School Reviewer (1875-1876)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the great love of Mihai Eminescu?",
        "difficult": "Easy",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Mirela",
          "Raluca",
          "Veronica"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Veronica"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where did Mihai Eminescu die?",
        "difficult": "Medium",
        "allAnswers": [
          "Bucharest",
          "Ipotesti",
          "Iasi"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Bucharest"
      }
    ]
  }